#### AMITKUMAR LEUVA

Full Stack Developer

+91 9033049648

amitleuva1987@gmail.com

https://github.com/amitleuva1987

Ahmedabad, INDIA

Senior web developer with over 10 years of web development experience, both technically focused and customer oriented. I believe in sustained improvement and finding better ways in doing things every day. i am looking for a career that is both challenging and reward.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCES**

### **Full Stack Developer**

Tagsen | Sept 2018 - March 2022

My roles and responsibilities with Tagsen.

- Database designing, Make coding
- Meeting with clients and understanding client requirements
- Making SRS (System requirement specification)
- Assigning work to the team members and look after their work
- Discussion with management and administration regarding company's growth

# **Full Stack Developer**

Brainspot Tech | Oct 2017 - Sept 2018

My roles and responsibilities with Brainspot Technologies.

- Make coding, designing database
- Meeting with clients and understanding client requirements
- Making reports and preparing project documents for the clients
- Discussion with management and administration regarding company's growth

# Senior Web Developer

Weblin Solutions | May 2015 - Jan 2017

My roles and responsibilities with Weblin Solutions.

- Making wordpress themes and plugins.
- Installing and customizing themes.
- Making reports and preparing project documents for the clients
- Discussion with management and administration regarding company's growth

### Web Developer

Kumbh Design | May 2010 - Apr 2015

#### SKILLS

### **Technical**

Laravel (version 5,6,7,8),
TDD with Laravel,
Codeigniter,
VueJS (Nuxt),
ReactJS (Next),
Jquery,
Wordpress,
Opencart,
Bootstrap (3,4,5)
Tailwind css
Mysql,

# **Professional**

**GIT** 

Team Player, Effective communication, Problem solver,

#### **EDUCATION**

BCA (Bachelor of computer applications), North Gujarat University, 2004 - 2007

## LANGUAGES

English, Hindi , My roles and responsibilities with Kumbh Design Inc.

- Make coding
- Responsible for dealing with clients (email and verbal communication)

Gujarati

### HOBBIES

Playing Cricket
Exploring new Technologies
Travelling

### **PROJECTS**

## Tagsen.com

Tagsen.com is an "online printing service" website. This website is created using Laravel 8. We have used laravel cashe and queue to boost the system. We have also used laravel notifications to notify customers and admin users. Razorpay payment gateway is intsalled to receive payments from the website.

## **Toplocal.in**

Toplocal.in is a website which provides local offers in the categories Food, Health, Fashion, Living and Business to our users. This website is built up using Codeigniter framework

## **Keyzone.in**

Keyzone.in is an ecommerce website which sells "Car key convers". This website is built up using Woocommerce. Initially, we integrated ccevenue payment gateway but later it was changed

# **Employee Project Board**

"Employee Project Board" is a system where all project of the company is being handled. All team members will be assigned to a project by the "Administrator". Each team member can login into the project board system can see his/her tasks (pending task and new task). Clients can also login into the system and see the progress of his/her project. Further, clients can directly deal with the team member and discuss regarding the issues with the project using a project thread.

# An ERP for Duke Pipes Pvt Ltd

This ERP consist of the following modules

- Employee Module
- Accounting Module
- Production Module
- Dealer Module
- Inventory and Scrappage
- Purchase
- Sales